a soldier an alchemist an archer and an
oddity a motley group we have assemble
here just as it has always been you
attract strange companions if we survive
the night this should be our last battle
no I cannot rest until we have justice
burr is a fearsome foe he may still get
the better of us I will get us home safe
as I always do why fight for this Lord
you have never cared much for the
nobility it is true but today we share a
common foe the Reaper
to finish this fight old friend let us
hope we have the strength to see it
through what treason brings you to
travel so far from home I was banished
from my home for taking my brother's
life I can never return
you say you do science the good doctor
Junkin Stein would profess the same
science is a tool and a method the hand
that wields it decides its course I once
met a man who could summon a dragon as
you do impossible
only my clan possesses the skill my
brother could but he is dead what
difference is there between the witch's
magic and your alchemy alchemy is a
science her magic is something darker
I sense that you and the soldier have
history together indeed and much of it
unhappy I can tell you and the soldier
have some history together this is not
office battle together I'm not the last
unless he does something foolish not
sure how I feel about all this alchemy
nonsense
seems like hocus-pocus to me I could
leave you to die if you prefer do you
think that was the last of them
Samson tells me the worst is yet to come
you do not trust my alchemy do you all
due respect witchcraft and magic potions
are no match for a good six shooter do
you think the doors would hold the doors
are not what I'm concerned about
sort of monster do you think the reaper
is the worst kind there is a wicked man
drives a man to such madness to be
tested
and to fail surely dr. Junkin Stein must
be running out of his machines he
strikes me as a man who had too many
three hours to invest in his pursuits my
people would call you a ronin a
masterless samurai Ronin I like the
sound of their what's home lag for you
Archer a village high atop the hill
cherry blossoms in the spring I miss it
dearly
you're not bad with a bow but don't you
think it's a little old fashioned
perhaps there's still a future for
anachronisms you think this lords good
for the money
castle looks like it's seen better days
if he breaks his world he has made some
powerful enemies hey Archer what say you
pass that flask around so we can all
have a drink this is thirsty work we
drink when the job is done
getting tired gunslinger not a chance
doesn't seem to be any end to the
monsters
let them come I could always use the
practice you seem awful familiar you
sure we haven't met before maybe in
another life
what was that thing um trying to put it
out of my mind
everyone's still alive that seems so
that or the after laughs a big
disappointment you ask me you pump
something fool these chemicals
electricity and what not as not a man
it's a monster maybe so
or maybe they're not as different as you
think
you don't seem like someone who'd put
his faith in the alchemy you have to
believe in something may as well be the
thing that keeps you alive so where are
you from back home I don't stay in one
place for too long came from a town
called Bloomington Indiana didn't expect
to find another American so far from
home do you fight in the war there's a
man like me fighting in every war